The overall result of SoLaMi SMILE and Dressing Pafé's competitions so far...
Is 50-50! But some day, I'll put an end to that!
How about not just "some day"
but at the upcoming Paprika Academy School Festival,
the Paprika Festival-pri?
Paprika Festival?
We'll have a contest event-pri.
Put screens all over the grounds and broadcast it live.
And the audience there will decide who wins.
That's what I like to hear.
But I can't imagine Headmistress Ookanda approving that.
The grounds are for the middle school's events. She's in charge of the elementary school.
Received and understood.
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
Received
and
understood
And as such...
we'll broadcast our shows at the Paprika Festival,
and have a contest between SoLaMi SMILE and Dressing Pafé.
That's right-pri!
Let's go all out. Let it GO!
Let's Pop Step Get that victory!
Capisce!
[catchphrases intensifying]
mirakuru☆paradaisu haato ni kizamo
Miracle☆paradise keep it in your heart
kisekiteki monogatari
A story of miracles
chiisana doryoku ga
A little effort will
mirai wo chenji hajimeyou
Change the future, let's start
Let's go! Let's go! nebagiba Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Never give up! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! minna de Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Everyone! Let's go!
Are you ready? Say! mirakuru paradaisu
Are you ready? Say! Miracle Paradise
koode bacchiri (bacchiri) fearii na wanpi de (wanpi de)
My coord's just right (just right), A fairy dress (fairy dress)
shisen atsumechau yo minna ni todoke kono Music
Catch everyone's eye, so they listen to this music
suteeji agareba (agareba) dare datte aidoru (aidoru)
Just get on the stage (on the stage) and you're an idol too (idol too)
joushoushikou de ikou
Let's get better every day
hoppu suteppu janpin!!
Hop step jumping!!
shippai shitari chotto hekondemo
Even when you mess up, and get a bit down
minna tomodachi
We're all friends
kirakira na meikingu dorama isshoni tsukurou
Let's make a sparkling Making Drama together
puripara paradaisu haato migaite
PriPara paradise polish your heart
yume wo kanaeru sekai
A world where dreams come true
aidoruranku wo agechaou
Let's grow our idol ranks
kirameki paradaisu donna toki mo
A shining paradise always every day
egao tayasazu ikou
Let's keep our smiles going
chiisana doryoku ga mirai wo chenji
A little effort will change the future
hajimeyou
Let's start!
Live at the School Festiva-kuma!
Hello. It's everyone's beloved elder brother, Akai Meganii.
I am here to present you a new song.
Ta-dah.
The new song is now registered in your PriPasses. The title: "Happy Hop Lucky"
And I took the liberty of booking your upcoming event.
I know you'll make my heart skip a beat.
Thank you so much!
Well, then:
A new song from me, to you:
Ta-da-da-dah.
Don't be shy now.
New song registered! Hot off the press!
We'll win for sure with this! More like SoLaMi Frown!
Right, Leona?
If you say so, Dorothy.
The title: "Change My World"
I'm looking forward to having my heart melted.
We'll do our best!
Thank you.
We'll definitely...
Win!
Yeah!
Go!
I have registered a number of new coords in honor of your new song.
Go on through the gate to try them on.
Thanks lots.
I can't wait to see them.
The Giraffe Dress.
So cute! Roar!
I don't think giraffes sound like that-kuma.
Fluffy Penguin Dress.
This poncho is like wings.
Roar! Roar!
Roar, roar... Are you even listening?
The Rainbow Diamond Dress.
My heart feels fancy!
The Forest Girl Dress.
Fantastic. The wind is calling for me.
The Dream Attendant Dress.
I feel like I can fly!
Star Dress.
I'll be the brightest star in the idol sky!
You're shining-kuma!
The Animal Dress.
Careful, I bite! Roar!
Wild-kuma!
The Sparkling Ramune Dress.
Ramune? How refreshing.
Cool-kuma!
None of these could lose to Dressing Pafé-kuma!
Come on then! Let's try them all on and decide on which ones to use today!
Cacacapisce!
So you're doing a show at the Paprika Festival?
Oh, you've already heard?
I know everything about PriPara.
I really would have preferred a Pink Actress show, though.
But I guess your show will have to do.
Good luck.
Capisce!
A PriPara concert!
A contest between SoLaMi SMILE and Dressing Pafé?
And exclusively for our school!
VIP treatment!
Seriously? Nice!
See how excited everyone is, Lala?
I can't wait either!
Thanks, Nao!
We'll make it the best concert ever, for the best festival ever!
Yeah! I'll be cheering for you!
Ding dong dong ding!
To everyone on the Disciplinary Committee and the Paprika Festival organizers:
Come to my office at once.
Ding dong dong dong.
Now, about this PriPara concert at the Paprika Festival...
I absolutely cannot allow this!
I would like to point out, Headmistress,
that the school grounds are reserved for the middle school branch's events.
And as such...
Having the approval of the middle school branch's Principal, it won't need my, Ookanda Gloria's, approval.
That's what you're saying, correct?
Correct.
She stands firm even against headmistress Ookanda!
That's our committee head!
Seems you're unaware of our rule 87.
87? "Students may not under any circumstances draw graffiti on the statue of the founder."
That's not the one.
Impossible, I have memorized the entire rulebook word for word.
I'm certain that was correct.
Oh, pardon me.
There are a number of rules you're unaware of.
That is?
A rulebook.
There's an additional rulebook?
There is indeed!
And these rules are known as:
The Principal's Rules!
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The
Principal's
Rules
The Principal's Rules?
Full of rules only I, the headmistress, know!
And article 87:
Paprika Festival events must obtain approval from both principal teachers regardless of location.
Article 87
Paprika Festival events
must obtain approval
from both principal teachers
regardless of location!
How can that...
Only you know? That's not playing fair!
As such, I veto the PriPara concert idea.
B-But the announcement has been made!
And the posters are...
You seem very invested in this, Minami.
Could it be that you have been going to PriPara?
That is irrelevant.
I am simply looking to make the Paprika Festival as successful as possible!
The students as well as their friends from elsewhere are looking forward to...
Neither PriPara nor friends are things our students need!
When I say "denied!" I mean denied.
Canceled? No way!
Eh?
What a shame.
After all the talk of having it under control...
You really are all talk.
Grasping at straws.
I'm out of ideas as well. So that's the end of that.
M-Minami...
I was really looking forward to the concert.
Leona?
Not even because I wanted us to win.
For all the elementary schoolers and boys who can't come to PriPara themselves...
I was hoping we could show them what it's like.
Well, yeah...
There it is!
Mi-Mireille!
Who's there?
I'm, uh... Mega-little-brother!
Mega-little-brother?
I want to see your concert! I mean the SoLaMi SMILE concert at Paprika Festival!
You know I'm an idol?
Please don't give up.
Head Disciplinarian...
No, Mireille!
I know you can find a way to make it happen in spite of the Principal's new rulebook!
Show us your brilliance!
Of course I will! I can do it.
I haven't given up. I've just been running calculations on how to turn it around.
Yes. Calculating.
And I have the perfect answer.
Mega-little-brother, go tell the rest of the committee
that we're helping make the concert happen.
Yes ma'am!
Thank you, Amamiya.
Good luck, Mireille!
Head Disciplinarian?
I have a way to get back at Ookanda fair and square!
Great.
Capisce!
Miss Meganee, we have a favor to ask!
You too?
Seems like...
We've reached the same conclusion.
Your request is regarding the Paprika Festival PriPara broadcast, yes?
Yes!
What a marvelous Paprika Festival.
I feel great after crushing that PriPara concert.
To everyone enjoying the Paprika Festival:
We are starting a special event soon!
Special event?
Come see the PriPara concert near the front gates!
Let's get hyped up!
PriPara concert?
It's not canceled?
Let's go!
Let's go too!
Yeah!
H-Hold it right there!
No one will make it past this line!
Right this way!
The show's over here!
You there! No pushing-chanko!
You kids! Return at once!
PriPara concert! I authorized no such thing!
Th-They have a permit!
Permit?
Th-The event is outside school grounds. Outside the bounds of the Principal's rules.
Just whose permit does this have then?
The police!
Police?
The event has all the proper permits in accordance with traffic law.
Prosecutor
Lawyer
And here's the relevant paperwork!
I've been thoroughly blindsided!
The crowd is all ready!
Just as planned-pri!
Where's it being shown?
Nothing here.
The PriPara trailer has arrived-chanko!
The plan went off without a hitch!
It's only just begun!
PriPara Trailer! Transform!
We're all ready-chanko!
Scan the appropriate amount of My Tickets for your coord.
You may also scan friend tickets.
Coord Change Start!
Dressing Pafé is using Fortune Party's number one seller, the Marching Star Coord.
Marching Star Coord!
Ladies and gentlemen of Paprika Academy, let's go wild!
Hi! Welcome to our PriPara concert!
Enjoy yourselves!
Dressing Pafé proudly presents:
Our new song: CHANGE! MY WORLD!
Shion!
Let's make dreams! We can do it!
Let's make dreams! Change my world!
kizuite shimattara mou tomaranai
There's no turning back once we start
atarashii sekai kitto ne tsukamaeru yo
Looking for a new world, and I know we'll find one
wakuwaku shichattara kitto we can't stop da ne
Once we start having fun I just know we can't stop
issho dattara watashi mo odoru ne
As long as we're together I can dance too
yume no door
The door of dreams
sanmi ittai de nara hiraku to shinjiteru
It will open for the three of us, I believe it will
dakara here we go
So here we go
naisho no passion
Our secret passion
jouseki datte kiseki ni kawaru hazu yo
Will turn our "run-of-the-mill" into miracles
tsuitekite yo ne
Come on along
tsuiteku ne
Come on
mahou mitai na PARTY TIME
To our magical PARTY TIME
dare datte minna motteru no
You and me, we all have one
hontou no jibun kagayaku place
A place where we can really shine
kaetai no nara
Want to change things?
negawanakya
Make a wish
sagashite
Look for it
kokoro no oku no omoi
A feeling from deep within
kanaete
Make it true
kakushiteta hontou no smile
The true smile you hid
osaerarenai yo
Can't be held back anymore
kitto minna
No one can
dakara jounetsu no mama
Give in to the passion and
Making Drama Switch On!
Sing! Sing!
utatte miyou
Let's sing together
kawatte iku kara my way
I'm changing! My way!
Girls and boys!
All the students at our school!
They're having fun!
That's wonderful!
Full-speed Dash!
Fly! Balloons!
akenakute namaru yori
Don't give up so fast
Cyalume Change!
watashi motte issho ni waraou
Come on and laugh with us
shiranakatta sekai ga
A world we never knew
yume no door
The door of dreams
Go!
Yay!
hiraita mukou ni
Revealed it to us
dare datte minna motteru no
You and me, we all have one
hontou no jibun kagayaku place
A place where we can really shine
mitsuketa no nara oshiete ne
If you found yours, do tell
negatta
If you wished
kokoro no oku no omoi
A feeling from deep within
kanaeyou
Make it true
kakusenai saikou no smile
The best smile is one you can't hide
afuredashichau yo
Can't contain
kitto minna
No one can
hora ne jounetsu no mama
So give in to the passion and
Sing! Sing!
utatte miyou
Let's sing together
kawatte ikun da my world
We're changing my world!
onna no ko mo
All you girls
otoko no ko mo
And boys too
utaou yo
Let's sing!
Let's change the world!
SoLaMi SMILE's new coords are based on festival snacks.
Cotton Candy Fluff Coord!
Popcorn Pompom Coord! Pri!
Chocolate Cream Blend Coord!
The show ain't over yet!
SoLaMi SMILE is here-pri!
With our new song, Happy Hop Lucky!
kanashii toki koso namida no koe kikou
Whenever you're sad, listen to those tears
kowakunai soba ni iru yo to kimi wa warattekureta
"Don't worry, I'm right here" you reassured me
ureshii toki ni wa hajikeru kodou ga
And when we're happy, and our hearts race
atarashii yume no tamago wo umu to oshiete kureta
You told me that eggs of new dreams will be born
daisuki yo daisuki da
Love you, love you lots
arigatou
Thank you
tabun ne kara zettai he to
From "maybe" to "definitely"
kawatteiku kankei tomaranai
This change we can't stop
josou wo tsukete kenpa kenpa happy heart
With a running start hopscotch hopscotch happy heart
kenken happy pa lucky
Hopscotch happy hop lucky
balance kuzushi korondemo ii yo
Off-balance and on the ground
nani mo akiramenai naru yo kami idol
But never give up, Divine Idols
Making Drama Switch On!
tokoton ga default desu ouen shite ne
We're going all the way, so cheer us on
hashiri tenpari tama ni yasunde
Running all the way, until our legs give out
Twirly twirl!
Sparkly sparkle!
acchi kocchi ni gottsun butsukari
Bumping head first into everything
dakara tonari ni ite ne
So don't fall behind
Deliver them to everyone!
Our feelings!
issho no omoide kyun kyun to marumete
Roll our good times into a nice tight bundle
And this complimentary Red Flash pizza!
Exciting... Present For You!
migaitara pikarin houseki
Polish it to a shine
mitai sono chikara wo takaku minagirou
like a precious gem, and feel the power overflow
Cyalume Change!
ne hora mae wo miyou
Hey, come on, face forward
kagayakaseru sa
Let's brighten the world
kami idol
Divine Idols
kenpa kenpa happy heart
Hopscotch hopscotch happy heart
kenken happy pa lucky
hop hop happy hop lucky
minna no chikara karitara dekiru yo
With your help we'll make it there
tanoshii no sono mata ue no sekai
A world above even "fun"
kanpeki janai kedo ne
We're not perfect yet
kanpeki mezasu
But we're gonna be
Lala!
Sophie!
PriPara...
M-My heart...
S-Stop this at once!
Return to school grounds at once!
Return at once!
Lady Sophie!
Chanko!
PriPara?! Friends?!
One day...
Even the headmistress will understand.
So it was another tie, but...
I'm glad they enjoyed us both.
Yeah, it was fun.
But we'll settle this yet.
Now your talking my language-pri!
I see how it is...
I have been too soft.
Time to take decisive action!
Until all trace of PriPara is gone from the world!
I'll definitely crush it this time!
Definitely! Definitely! Definitely! Definitely!
Definitely! Definitely!
Remember PriPara!
kirakira kiranwei
Shining sparkling runway
zutto kagayaite (Yeah!)
Keep on shining (Yeah!)
chiisana mune ga dokin♪tte ne
My tiny heart's going♪badump
shuwashuwa no saidaa mitai ni
I'm bubbling like a glass of cider
odoridashitara
When the dancing starts
mahou ni kakaru aizu
You'll be under a spell
honno sukoshi no yuuki to
Show a little bit of courage
kakaekirenai yume dake motte
Only bring the dreams that are too big
Let's GO! gaman shinaide
Let's GO! Don't hold back
himitsu no geeto kugurou
Let's go through this secret gate
senobi shite oshare shite
Get taller, get fashionable
mada shiranai sekai
A whole new world
atarashii jibun ni nareru basho matteru yo
I'm waiting for a place where I can be reborn
kirakira kiranwei zutto
The shining sparkling runway
hoshizora yori mo kagayaite
Outshining all the stars in the sky
kimi to hanbunko ni shita yume
The dream we shared that day
kanaete kurerun da (Yeah!)
Is finally coming true (Yeah!)
kirakira kiranwei kitto
The shining sparkling runway, is surely
mirai he to nobiru kakehashi
A bridge leading to the future
namida mo egao mo tsunaidara
Connecting our happiness and our tears
watatte ikerun da (Yes!)
We can cross over (Yes!)
kimi mo issho ni tsuretette ageru yo
And you can come along with us too
hikari ni tsutsumareru sekai
Into the world bathed in light
Next Episode Preview
Remember PriPara.
I've made my decision.
I will erase the word PriPara from my school!
What? Ookanda is becoming the middle school's principal too?
To all students:
From now on, going to PriPara is forbidden for all students!
Oh no! No one will be able to go to PriPara!
Next time: The Last Day of PriPara!
The Last Day of PriPara
Go for it! Let's go! PriPara!